There's nothing quite like new clothes, is there?
没什么能比得上新衣服带来的快乐，不是吗？
The UK certainly loves them.
英国人肯定是喜欢的。
According to a report by the Environmental Audit Committee (EAC), the UK consumes five times more clothes today than it did in the 1980s. That's more than any other nation in Europe and amounts to around 26.7kgs per person.
英国环境审计委员会（EAC）的一份报告显示，如今英国人的服装消费量是20世纪80年代的五倍，这一数值超过了欧洲其他任何国家，人均年服装消费量约为26.7公斤。
This results in 235 million garments going to landfill – victims of fast fashion.
这导致每年有2.35亿件衣物被送进垃圾填埋场——它们都是快时尚的牺牲品。
Fast fashion is defined as “an accelerated fashion business model” involving “increased numbers of new fashion collections every year”, “quick turnarounds” and “lower prices”, according to the EAC.
英国环境审计委员会将快时尚定义为一种“快速的时尚商业模式”，其特点是“每年推出的新服装系列数量不断增加”“周转周期短”以及“售价低廉”。
Globalisation means that attire is made in countries where labour is cheaper.
全球化使得服装被转移到劳动力成本更低的国家生产，而由此节省的成本会转嫁给消费者。
This saving is passed on to consumers, who then consider the garb they own disposable – easily replaceable with something more on-trend. And that creates problems.
这让消费者将自己的衣物视为一次性用品——很容易就会被更时髦的款式取代，而这便引发了一系列问题。
First, there's the environmental cost.
首先是环境成本问题。
Manufacturing any kind of textile costs resources.
生产任何纺织品都要消耗大量资源。
For example, synthetic fibres, which are made from plastic, have a larger carbon footprint than natural ones.
例如，塑料制成的合成纤维，其碳足迹要大于天然纤维。
Natural fibres, although more carbon-efficient, still require more water to grow.
而天然纤维虽然更低碳，但种植过程需要消耗更多水资源。
And further resources are used as the cloth is dyed, made into clothing and transported to retail for sale.
此外，布料的染色、成衣制作以及运输到零售终端销售的各个环节，都会消耗更多资源。
Secondly, the fast-fashion industry is under pressure to put the latest trending items on shelves fast, which can lead to workers being exploited and forced to labour in poor working conditions.
其次，快时尚行业面临着快速将最新潮流单品上架的压力，这可能导致工人遭受剥削，被迫在恶劣的工作环境中劳作。
In countries such as Bangladesh, Ethiopia and the Philippines, workers are paid wages that are insufficient to live on.
在孟加拉国、埃塞俄比亚和菲律宾等国家，工人的工资难以维持基本生活。
One worker in Ethiopia told the BBC that they had to deal with intolerable conditions, such as withheld overtime payments, verbal abuse, and unsanitary toilets.
一名埃塞俄比亚工人向英国广播公司透露，他们不得不忍受难以容忍的工作条件，比如加班费被克扣、遭受言语辱骂，以及厕所卫生条件极差等。
So what can be done in the UK to reduce clothes waste?
那么，英国可以采取哪些措施来减少衣物浪费呢？
The EAC has recommended eighteen improvements to the UK government, from increasing tax on purchases to fund recycling centres to introducing more sewing lessons in schools, encouraging a make do and mend attitude when things become threadbare.
英国环境审计委员会向政府提出了18项改进建议，包括提高服装购买税以资助回收中心、在学校增设缝纫课程，以及鼓励人们在衣物破旧后秉持“修修补补凑合用”的态度。
What can we do?
我们个人又能做些什么呢？
Shop “second-hand and vintage,” recommends Tolly Gregory, an ethical fashion blogger.
环保时尚博主托莉·格雷戈里建议大家“购买二手和复古衣物”。
Kristabel Plummer, a London-based fashion blogger, who spoke to the BBC, also recommends “looking for quality” and “longevity”.
伦敦时尚博主克里斯塔贝尔·普拉默在接受英国广播公司采访时也建议，要“注重服装质量”和“耐用性”。
So keep an eye out for durable, resilient, hardy apparel that resists wear and tear.
因此，我们应该留意那些结实耐穿、不易磨损的衣物。